DHONA O. OBINA

+64 27 555 8668	O Canterbury, New Zealand 7630	www.linkedin.com/in/dhonaobina
Dhona.Obina@outlook.com		https://dhonaobina.github.io/

CAREER OBJECTIVE

With a decade of Customer Service experience and a current role as a Delivery Lead and Service Desk Analyst, I am a qualified IT professional with a New Zealand Certification for IT Essentials Level 4. I have recently completed advanced courses in front-end and backend development. I am passionate about learning new technologies and becoming a full stack developer. I am looking for an opportunity to join a reputable coding institution where I can apply my skills and knowledge, learn from experienced developers, and make a positive impact in the community.

EDUCATION

June 2022 - PRESENT - Code + | Full Stack Developer

Learning People Global - Christchurch, New Zealand

Sept 2021 - June 2022 - New Zealand Certificate in IT Essentials | NZQA Level 4

ARA Institute of Canterbury, Christchurch, New Zealan

CORE SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | JavaScript
- Knowledge MongoDB | Express | NodeJS
- Angular | React
- Bootstrap
- Git & GitHub
- Salesforce | Microsoft Office 365
- Knowledge in Python | SQL

CERTIFICATIONS

- Web Design: Efficient Workflow
- Software Project Management Foundations
- Software Development Life Cycle
- Programming Foundation Fundamentals
- Business Writing Principles
- Information Literacy
- Please check my LinkedIn for new updates...

WORK HISTORY

P & L Limited | SPARK BUSINESS New Zealand

Service Desk Analyst || October 2022 - Present

- Providing first and second level technical support to end-users, troubleshooting
 issues, and escalating complex problems to the appropriate teams as needed. I have
 excellent communication skills, patience, and a customer-first mindset.
- Documenting and tracking customer issues in a ticketing system, managing all tickets through Jira or Confluence, and ensuring all tasks are completed accurately and before deadline.
- Assisting in Point-of-Sale Software to ensure maximum efficiency and maintenance, supporting CRM and

integrations, and coding for cloud, on-premises, and device environments.

- Assisting with management and co-ordination of company's environment & integration for POS & Xero, working closely with business system team and application partners.
- Optimizing the efficiency of reporting functions, assisting Business Analyst with mapping, project planning, gathering technical and business requirements, and performing data and SQL query analysis.

Focus Delivery Lead || March 2018 - Present

- Taking ownership of sales orders proactively liaising with account managers to ensure they are well informed of the status of their request.
- Ensures that services are delivered by meeting agreed SLA and performance targets.
- Accurately process and manage simple to complex provisioning order on behalf of 12 Regions supporting Small Medium Enterprise in New Zealand – in particular, Mobiles, Landlines and Broadband
- Participates in constructive one-on-one and team meetings with colleagues, stakeholders, Customer and Site Lead including regional managers.
- Mentoring newly hired colleagues in BAU processes and procedures to various application and service orders
- Created a process for Spark Hardware and Accessory for better orders management.
- Experience with Salesforce, Siebel, ICMS for Customer Relationship Management.

SPARK New Zealand Limited

Customer Solutions Specialist | | Sept 2015 - March 2018

- Built and maintained business relationships with consumer clients by providing prompt and accurate service to promote customer loyalty.
- Ensured Targets are attained for the success of the business.
- Worked precisely when processing orders through ICMS and Spark CRM.
- Helped customer's billing, services and issues including complaint and delivered best resolution.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Content creation, Helping family and friends with digital marketing and photography on my free time.